(Bernadette:)Are you sure you guys don't
want to come with us to Napa?
(Bernadette:)You could probably still get a room.
(Penny:)No, I think we're just gonna
have a quiet weekend at home.
(Leonard:)Plus, I'm not sure it's a great idea
(Leonard:)to take Penny
to where wine comes from.
(Leonard:)What? It's a joke.
(Leonard:)Oh, come on.
We bust on each other.
(Leonard:)I wear dorky glasses,
you might have a problem.
(Leonard:)It's all for laughs.
(Penny:)That would really piss me off if
I didn't have a buzz going on.
(Sheldon:)Howard, which pocket watch will you
be wearing for dinner on the train?
(Howard:)I'm sorry, what?
(Sheldon:)I'm afraid if we wear
the same pocket watch,
(Sheldon:)it will be embarrassing.
(Howard:)I don't own a pocket watch.
(Sheldon:)Oh, my.
(Sheldon:)Well, then my apologies
for bringing up this sore spot.